Guide to the Michael Bennett Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Material, 1966-circa 1986; Series III; 5 linear feet (5 boxes)
  - Audiocassettes, circa 1973-1986; 165; Includes 3 empty cassette cases
    - Gallery, The "A" Reel, I, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971599)
    - Gallery, The "B" Reel, II, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971607)
    - Potpourri of background music from "Mime" and dance musical "Thy Giantkeepers", undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971490)
    - Dance music, four eights, 9 eights, 7 eights, four eights, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971508)
    - Final aria, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971532)
    - music and mirror, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971540)
    - For Michael - Christine rock for Psalms / Work Tape, S. Lake Narr, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971557)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971565)
    - "Lucky Guy" by Willard Beckham, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971573)
      A list of contents is included.
      Act I / Act II
      1. Big Al
      2. Osage County Line
      3. Other Folks' Dreams
      4. Lucky Guy
      5. Blue Jean Blues
      6. Needle in a Haystack
      7. Queen of Country Music
      8. Do What You Can Do
      1. Blue Jean Blues (Rep.)
      2. Yo' a Little Lady
      3. Make Up His Mind
      4. Trailer Park Romance
      5. I Wonder Why
      6. Chicky
      7. My Old Friend
    - "Just So!", undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971581)
      Just So
      Camel Blues
      Until Tomorrow
      Dessert, Dessert
      Eat, Eat, Eat
      Arm in Arm in Harmony
      I Have Changed
      Everything Under the Sun
    - "One & Only", Act I, Mat., 1983 April 13; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971615)
    - "We're Movin' Up!", Betty K. Bynum, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971623)
    - Gallery, The "A" Reel, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971631)
    - Gallery, The "B" Reel, II, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971649)
    - Gallery, The "B" Reel, II, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971656)
    - Gallery, The "A" Reel, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971664)
    - Rewrites for NYSF Workshop "Gallery", 10 songs, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971672)
    - Rewrites for NYSF Workshop "Gallery", 10 songs, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971680)
    - Rewrites for NYSF Workshop "Gallery", 10 songs, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971698)
    - Jan M. Warner. 30 songs on Demonstration Cassette, 1977 August; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971706)
      "The Mornin' Ain't the Same Without You Next to Me" (Alan)
      "Love Can Happen at the Drop of a Hat" (Burns)
      "Let Me Down Slowly" (Deneroff)
      "Good Morning Midnight" (Alan)
      "Another Letter" (Alan)
      "Savannah Sunshine" (Alan)
      "Lookin' for a Better Day, The Lord has Sent You My Way" (Sandy Toder)
      "Anything Goes" (Calello)
      "No One but the One I Love" (Burns)
      "You've Been Makin' Love to My Mind" (Deneroff)
      "You're Slippin' Through my Fingers" (Snyder)
      "I was Never One to Fall in Love Overnight" (Levine)
      "Let's Make Love One More Time with Feeling" (Levine)
      Excerpt from "Now that We're Lovers" (Burns)
      Excerpt from "If I Told You" (Hillman)
      "There's Nobody But You" (Levine)
      "Damned if I Do - Damned if I Don't (Levine)
      "I'm on My Way to Jacksonville" (Alan)
      "Always a Little Ahead of My Time" (Hillman)
      "Sorry 'Bout That" (Burns)
      "Anything for Your Love" (Cooke)
      "Didn't Know You had It in You" (Burns)
      "That's What You Get for Loving Me" (Smith)
      "Why'd You have to Go and Kill a Good Thing" (Deneroff)
      "You Got Right Thru to Me" (Deneroff)
      "Tomorrow's Goin' to Bring Me Love" (Hillman)
      "When Youth is in the Blood" (Hawdon)
      "Oh Lovely Day" (Hillman)
      "I'll Send for You" (Deneroff)
      "I Couldn't Stay in Line" (Deneroff)
    - Boston Story, Act 2, 1974 July 8; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971714)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971722)
    - Bus and Truck, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971730)
    - Williard Beckham. "Lucky Guy", Act I and II, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971748)
      Side A / Side B
      1. Maybe Girl
      2. Blue Jean Blues (Rep.)
      3. Yo' a Little Lady
      4. Make Up His Mind
      5. Trailer Park Romance
      6. I Wonder Why
      7. Chicky
      8. My Old Friend
    - Jon Rome. 1. The Occupation Song 2. The Meek Shall Insherit the Earth, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971755)
    - Arthur Siccardi, Carpenter. Vienna, 1979 January 23-24; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971763)
    - Arthur Siccardi, Carpenter. Oktober Theatre, Kiev (also, opera studio), Leningrad, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971771)
    - Arthur Siccardi, Carpenter. Moscow, Mahat Theatre / "Gin Game" - interview with crew, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971789)
    - Arthur Siccardi, Carpenter. Leningrad, Opera Studio, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971797)
    - Bee Gees. "To Whom It May Concern", 1972; 1 (Box 53)
    - "Oh Brother" cast album with Judy Kaye, Alan Weeks, D.J. Carrol, Harry Groner, and Joe Morton. Peter Hammer - drums, 1982 October 12; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971805)
      A handwritten note is included with this audiocassette. It reads: Dear Michael, I thought that I would send you a tape of the "Oh Brother" album so you could hear what I've been up to lately. It was recorded last October so it is a fairly recent example. Anyway I hope you enjoy it and it disproves all of the nasty things that Messers. Thomas and Tunick say about my playing. Thanks, Peter
    - "Marry Me a Little", undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971813)
    - "America Loves a Humbug", undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971821)
    - Liz Swados. "Jerusalem", part III of III, 1985 June 11; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971839)
    - "Legs Diamond" - Act I, II, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971847)
    - Dreamgirls, undated; 1 (Box 53)
      This is a commercial audiocassette and a duplicate. It has not been digitized.
    - Linda Somers, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971854)
    - Liz Swados. "Jerusalem", part I of III, 1985 June 11; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971862)
    - Nickolaus, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971870)
    - Jim Polles. All songs, 1984; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971888)
      1. You Want It All
      2. Think About You
      3. Lifeline
      4. You Won't Be Lonely
      5. Private Signals
      6. Busy Tonight
      7. Everybody Needs a Helpin' Hand
    - Songs from "Who's Papa" by Michael Penetar, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971896)
      1. Madeira Rosa
      2. Madeira Waltz
      3. My Friend the Dentist
      4. I'm a 19th Century Woman
      5. Who's Papa
      6. Oh! Mr. Valentine
      7. Please Tell Them
      8. Must Have Made an Impression on You
      9. When You Marry
      10. Teddy Bear Song
      11. I'll Love You Just the Same
      12. Vienna
      13. I Love You So
    - An evening of just a few but terrific realizations! Hurray!, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971904)
    - Blondel, original London cast, 1983; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971912)
      1. Monks' Introduction
      2. Blondel and Fiona
      3. The Ministry of Feudal Affairs
      1. The Least of My Troubles
      2. Lionheart
      3. No Rhyme for Richard
      4. Trio
      5. Assassin's Song
      6. Running Back for More
    - DG Fashion Show, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971920)
    - Dreamgirls review, 1982; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971938)
    - Act II opening, 1983 February 23; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971946)
    - Act II, Sc 3-with cuts, MB working II-3; end tape-"Waitin for a Man"...Act II, 1981 January 22; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971953)
    - Project #9, copy 3, 1980 August 21; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971961)
    - Act II, Sc. 7; Working Curtis/cc, 1981 February 3; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971979)
    - Michael Bennett, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971987)
    - Dreamgirls, 5 spots, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971995)
    - Follies, III and IV, 1985 June 28; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109972001)
    - "Dream Girl" produced by Serino Coyne Nappi, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109972019)
    - Dreamgirls, National Public Radio produced by Tom Vitale, 1982 February 4; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109972027)
    - PG Ref Tape, Music Review Act I, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109972035)
    - Side "A", now Rap. "Orchestra Rehearsal"... / Rap. II, Sc. 3, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109972043)
    - Final Workshop Performance, Act I, #6, 1981 April 10; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109972050)
    - Heavy Reh. Tape / New Act II opening, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109972068)
    - Arrangements by Carl Maultsby, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109972076)
    - Reference Tape, 1981 March 27; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109972084)
    - Act I of runthrough on side I, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109972092)
    - Dreamgirls Fashion Show, medley etc., 1982 September 9; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109972100)
    - Big Dreams, #2 of day, 1981 February 12; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109972118)
    - New - End of Act II, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109972126)
    - Dreamgirls, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109972134)
    - Act II, scenes 3, 4, 5, 1981 January 31; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109972142)
    - Jimmy Webb. "Here I Am", November 15; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109972159)
  - Video Recordings
    - "A Chorus Line, The Movie" Auditions, 1984 February; YCALMSS538_0001; 1; 00:54:55 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102301877)
      1) Channel 7 Eyewitness Extra 4-5 pm 2/24/84 2) Channel 2 "6 o'clock news" 2/24/84 (D. Cunningham) 3) Channel 5 "10 o'clock news" 2/24/84 (S. Klein) 4) Channel 7 "Entertainment Tonight" 7:30-8pm 2/27/84
    - A Chorus Line TV coverage cassette #2, undated; YCALMSS538_0002; 1; 00:43:33 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102301885)
      Coverage listed with the tape.
      "Chorus Line"
      CBS Network News, 09-29, Thurs., 7 p.m.
      NBC Network News, 09-29, Thurs., 7 p.m.
      WABC-TV, Entertainment Tonight, 09-29, Thurs., 7:30 p.m.
      WNEW-TV, 10 O'Clock News, 09-29, Thurs., 10 p.m.
      WPIX-TV, Independent Network News, 09-29, Thurs., 10 p.m.
      WNBC-TV, NBC Net, Live and In Person, 09-29, Thurs., 10 p.m.
      WCBS-TV, Channel Two News, 09-29, Thurs., 10 p.m.
      WNBC-TV, News Four New York, 09-29, Thurs., 11 p.m.
      WABC-TV, Eyewitness News, 09-29, Thurs., 11 p.m.
      WPIX-TV, Late News Final, 09-30, Friday, 1:30 a.m.
      CBS Network, Night Watch, 09-30, Friday, 2 a.m.
      NBC Network, News Overnight, 09-30, Friday, 2 a.m.
    - A Chorus Line TV coverage cassette #3, undated; YCALMSS538_0003; 1; 00:41:42 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102301893)
      NBC Network, News Overnight, 09-[30], Friday, 1:30 a.m.
      CBS Network, Nightwatch, 09-30, Friday, 2:00 a.m.
      ESPN-TV, Business Times, 09-30, Friday, 6:00 a.m.
      WABC-TV, News, 09-30, Friday, 6:25 a.m.
      WABC-TV, News, 09-30, Friday, 7:25 a.m.
      WABC-TV, News, 09-30, Friday, 8:25 a.m.
      WOR-TV, News, 09-30, Friday, Noon
      WCBS-TV, Newsbreaker, 09-30, Friday, 5:00 p.m.
      WCBS-TV, Channel Two News, 09-30, Friday, 6:00 p.m.
      WABC-TV, Entertainment Tonight, 09-30, Friday, 7:30 p.m.
      CBS Morning News, 09-29, Thurs., 7 a.m.
      ABC Network, Good Morning America, 09-29, Thurs., 8 a.m.
      NBC Network, Sunrise, 09-30, Friday, 6:30 a.m.
      WPIX-TV, Independent Network News, 09-30, Friday, 12:30 p.m.
    - A Chorus Line TV coverage cassette #1, undated; YCALMSS538_0004; 1; 00:54:46 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102301901)
      A list of coverage is included with the tape.
      WCBS-TV, Newsbreaker Report, 09-28, Wednesday, 5 p.m. - Michael Bennett
      WNBC-TV, Today, 09-29, Thursday, 8 a.m. - Chorus Line
      WABC-TV, Morning Show, 09-29, Thursday, 9 a.m.
      WABC-TV, Eyewitness News, 09-29, Thursday, 9 a.m.
      WABC-TV, Eyewitness News, 09-29, Thursday, 5 p.m.
      WABC-TV, Eyewitness News, 09-29, Thursday, 6 p.m.
      WCBS-TV, Channel Two News, 09-29, Thurs., 5 p.m.
      WNBC-TV, Live at Five, 09-29, Thurs., 5 p.m.
      WNBC-TV, News Four New York, 09-29, Thursday, 6 p.m.
    - A Chorus Line TV coverage cassette #4, undated; YCALMSS538_0005; 1; 00:19:08 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102301919)
      A note on "Chorus Line" coverage from across the country is included. The list is broken down into regions.
      Detroit
      1. WXYZ-TV Action News, 5 p.m., 1983-09-29
      2. WJBK-TV Eyewitness News, Noon, 1983-09-30
      3. WDIV-TV News Four, Noon, 1983-09-30
      Los Angeles
      1. Channel 2 News, KNXT_TV, Thursday, 1983-09-29, 6 p.m.
      2. News at Ten, KTLA-TV, Thursday, 1983-09-29, 10 p.m.
      Chicago, 1983-09-29
      Channel Two News, WBBM-TV, 10 p.m.
      Newscenter, WMAQ-TV, 10 p.m.
      Eyewitness News, WLS-TV, 4:30 p.m.
      Eyewitness News, WLS-TV, 6 p.m.
      [Newsninew], GN-TV, 9 p.m.
      Washington, D.C., 1983-09-29
      1. WRC-TV (4) News, 5:30 p.m.
      2. Metromedia News, WTTG-TV (5), 10 p.m.
      3. WJLA-TV (7) News, 11 p.m.
    - "Schubert Theatre-Dream Girls" Eyewitness News, WLS-TV Chicago 10:30 PM 00:51, 1984 April 4; YCALMSS538_0006; 1; 00:02:01 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102301927)
    - Dreamgirls, raw footage, tapes #1 & 2, WJAR-TV, 1985 October 8; YCALMSS538_0007; 1; 00:28:20 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102301935)
    - Dreamgirls, 2 On the Town, CBS/KNXT, undated; YCALMSS538_0008; 1; 00:07:51 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102301943)
    - Lillias White-"Dreamgirls" Mid-Morning L.A., KHJ-TV Ch.9, 10 am, 1983 July 27; YCALMSS538_0009; 1; 00:09:09 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102301950)
    - Hullaballoo 3-23-65: The Hullabaloo Dancers, 1965-1983; YCALMSS538_0010; 1; 02:30:58 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102301968)
      "A Chorus Line" Reunion ("Live and In Person"); "Dreamgirls" ("Live and In Person") 9-27-83 ("The Tonight Show"); "Jennifer Holiday-Inn;" Charles Pierce 10-28-83 (Studio One Backlot); Marvin Hamlisch; Hullabaloo 3-23-65 Hits of the Day including Leslie Uggamsy Gere Pitney, Dear Jones; "Carmen" the movie
    - Murray Head "Pity the Child", undated; YCALMSS538_0011; 1; 00:07:25 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102301976)
    - CBS "Two on the Town" Willa Shalit Lifecasting, 1984 January; YCALMSS538_0012; 1; 00:08:44 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102301984)
    - "KUP and Today in chi; 4/7 and 4/9", undated; YCALMSS538_0013; 1; 01:31:17; Video is very poor. There are problems, mostly at the beginning of the tape, with video cutting out. Sound does continue throughout the tape. (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102301992)
    - "M. Korshak", undated; YCALMSS538_0014; 1; 00:07:22 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102302008)
      1) Ch 2 6-7 4/4; 2) Ch 5 6-6:30 4/4; 3) Ch 7 4-5 4/5
    - Serino, Coyne and Nappi, "A Chorus Line", 1983 June 3; YCALMSS538_0015; 1; 00:01:13 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102302016)
      "The Only One" :10; "Longest Musical Ever"; :30
    - Dreamgirls from "Live... And in Person", undated; YCALMSS538_0016; 1; 00:05:45 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102302024)
    - Serino, Coyne and Nappi "A Chorus Line", 1983 May 31; YCALMSS538_0017; 1; 00:02:51 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102302032)
      "Longest Musical Ever" :30; "The Only One" :10
    - Ralph Lauren fall fashion show, LCL Productions, 1982; YCALMSS538_0018; 1; 00:37:05 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102302040)
    - Ralph Lauren, 1982; YCALMSS538_0019; 1; 00:26:01 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102302057)
      1. Ralph Lauren (3 parts) a. Ralph interview b. Models c. Fashions; 2. Ralph Lauren-"Hour Magazine"; 3. R. Lauren Fall Fashion Show
    - 1976 Tony Awards History, Part #1, YCALMSS538_0020; 1; 01:02:58 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102302065)
      Bentwood Television Corp.
    - Baryshnikov on Broadway (in full cast finale "One" from A Chorus Line), special aired 4/24/80 9pm Ch. 7 ABC-TV, 1980 April 24; YCALMSS538_0021; 1; 00:52:40 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102302073)
    - Baryshnikov on Broadway (w/billboards-no commercials), 1980 April 14; YCALMSS538_0022; 1; 00:53:24 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102302081)
    - Paul Anka...Jubilation, undated; YCALMSS538_0023; 1; 00:08:05 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102302099)
    - Dennis Cunningham Benefit, undated; YCALMSS538_0024; 1; 00:03:52 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002102302107)
    - 1976 Tony Awards History, Part #1 A, YCALMSS538_0025; 1; 00:30:44 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002102302115)
    - 1976 Tony Awards History, Part #2, YCALMSS538_0026; 1; 01:01:32 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002102302123)
    - 1976 Tony Awards #3, YCALMSS538_0027; 1; 00:08:33 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002102302131)
    - "A Chorus Line/Chicago", 1978 September 29; YCALMSS538_0028; 1; 00:01:24 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002102302149)
    - Case and McGrath, A Chorus Line, 1976 November 17; YCALMSS538_0029; 1; 00:02:11 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002102302156)
      1. CH-L-TV-1-60 "A Chorus Line: :60; 2. CH-L-TV-2-30 "A Chorus Line" :30
  - Audiotape Reels, 1966-1986; 18; Includes an empty reel and two empty storage boxes
    Box 68: Restricted Fragile material. Access to original audio tapes is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Contact Access Services for further information.
    - Ballroom master #4, score, 1978 August 10; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002109970161)
      A list of contents of this audiotape reel are included.
      Opening - Who Gave You Permission
      Job Application
      Song for Dancing - Foxtrot
      Samba
      Rhumba
      Lindy
      Cha-Cha Montage
      Dreams-Goodnight (inst.)
      Somebody Did Alright
      Permission (reprise)
      Tango
      Goodnight
      Like Her
      Where Have You Been/She's Late
      Nomination Music
      50%/Waltz
      Waltz Finale/I Love to Dance
      Where Have You Been
    - Ballroom master tape #1, Ballroom score 5/9/78, Foxtrot and montage / various rehearsal pieces and cut music, 1978 May 29; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002109970179)
      A list of contents is included with this audiotape reel.
      Stardust Waltz
      Kaddish/My Father/Permission
      Dreams
      Permission Reprise
      Fifty Percent
      I Love to Dance/Finale
      Foxtrot (Ballroom 1)
      Montage-Ballroom 1
      Lindy Music
      Family Council
      Dreams - vocal and underscore
      Stardust Waltz - up tempo, slow tempo
      Kaddish - work tape
      Kaddish - rehearsal tape
      Rehearsal music
    - Milliken #2, 1966 June 8; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002109970187)
    - Ballroom, undated; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002109970195)
      A list of contents are included with this audiotape reel.
      Who Gave You Permission?
      Pennies and Dreams
      The Peabody
      Call Me a Fool
      Who Gave You Permission (reprise), A Big Mistake, tango
      Suddenly There's You
      Dance Montage: Foxtrot, Cha-Cha, Lindy
      I Love to Dance/Stardust Waltz (fade out version
    - Up on the Mountain, undated; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002109970203)
      Side II
      Che Che Che
      Pants Dropping Dance
      Once We Danced
      War on the Mountain
      Up You Go My Darling
      Fathers and Daughters
      Sunday Morning
    - Ballroom master tape #2 - Kaddish rehearsal, rehearsal music and orig. songs / rehearsal music, Stardust Ballroom - T.V. sdtk., 1978 May 29; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002109970211)
      Kaddish rehearsal
      Permission
      Dreams (again)
      Johnny Mathis Lindy's
      Guys and Dolls
      I Like It
      Song
      Cha-Cha
      I Love to Dance
      Over Here
      Chatanooga Choo-Choo
      Gal in Kalamazoo
      Permission, Big Mistake, Tango
      Montage
      I Love to Dance/Waltz
    - Ballroom master tape #3 - Ballroom reading, 1978 June 24-26; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002109970229)
      Ballroom readings with Dorothy Loudon and Vincent Gardenia
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002109970237)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002109970245)
    - Atina: Evil Queen of the Galaxy, reel 2, 1980; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002109970252)
      Born Evil
      Atina's Battle Cry
      Dinner for my Poopsie
      I Hate the Bitch
      The Transformation of the Octopus Woman
      Tomorrow the Galaxy
    - "Always Mademoiselle" from "Coco", undated; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002109970260)
    - A Chorus Line, 1980 January 4; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002109970278)
    - Tape #1, EYEN Project, April 6-7; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002109970286)
    - Fonda Fashion Show-Fashion Masters, 1983 November 7; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002109970294)
    - EYEN Project, tape #3 - 1st run thru, 4th workshop, 1981 April 9; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002109970302)
    - EYEN Project rehearsal, tape 2, 1981 April 6-8; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002109970310)
    - Side 1, run thru #2 of EYEN Project, [1981] April 10; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002109970328)
- Oversize Material, 3.25 linear feet (13 boxes)
  - Dreamgirls, bound music score (Series I.), 1984 (Box 56)
  - Company, bound music score (Series I.), 1971 (Box 56)
  - A Chorus Line, bound music score (Series I.), undated (Box 57)
  - Follies, bound music score (Series I.), 1971 (Box 57)
  - A Chorus Line, photographs, newspaper clippings, and "Dreamgirls Day" proclamation (Series I.), circa 1976-1986; 9 (Box 58)
  - A Chorus Line, photographs, Ballroom photographs and personal photographs (Series I.), circa 1976-1986; 6 (Box 59)
  - Scrapbooks (Series I.), circa 1976-1986; 2 (Box 60)
  - Posters (Series I.), circa 1973-1986; 3 (Box 61)
  - Framed items (Series II.), undated; 4 (Box 62)
  - Framed photographs (Series II.), undated; 4 (Box 63)
  - Awards (Series II.), 1976-1979; 2 (Box 64)
  - Gold and platinum records for A Chorus Line (Series II.), undated; 2 (Box 65)
  - Drama Critics Circle Award for A Chorus Line (Series II.), 1975 (Box 66)
  - Framed Follies poster (Series II.), undated (Box 66)
  - Engraved silver plates (Series II.), undated; 4 (Box 67)